Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Twin Fates=
=مصيران توأمان=
=Episode 7= (Twin Cultivation on Full Moon Night)
=الحلقة 7= (زراعة التوأم في ليلة اكتمال القمر)
(Why is my face so red?)
(لماذا وجهي أحمر هكذا؟)
(What am I even thinking?)
(ماذا أفكر حتى؟)
(Calm down.)
(اهدأ.)
(It's the Silver Fox Clan scent.)
(إنها رائحة عشيرة الثعلب الفضي.)
(I knew there was a hidden chamber.)
(كنت أعلم أن هناك غرفة مخفية.)
(The account might be hidden here.)
(قد يكون الحساب مخفيًا هنا.)
(Oh no.)
(أوه لا.)
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I didn't summon you.
لم أدعوك
I'll be careful.
سوف أكون حذرا.
You...
أنت...
What are you doing in the study?
ماذا تفعل في الدراسة؟
It was Lord Yi who framed my father
لقد كان اللورد يي هو الذي أوقع والدي في الفخ.
and got my whole family executed.
وأعدمت عائلتي بأكملها.
I came to Lord Yi's Residence
لقد جئت إلى مقر إقامة اللورد يي
for one reason only.
لسبب واحد فقط.
I want to avenge the Mu family.
أريد الانتقام لعائلة مو.
If that's so,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
I'll help you kill him.
سأساعدك على قتله.
I want blood for blood,
أريد الدم مقابل الدم،
but more than that, I want to clear our name.
ولكن أكثر من ذلك، أريد أن أبريء اسمنا.
I must find the evidence
يجب أن أجد الدليل
that he framed my father
أنه أوقع والدي في الفخ
and prove the Mu family's innocence.
وإثبات براءة عائلة مو.
I just tested Ji Yuanying
لقد اختبرت للتو جي Yuanying
and found out there maybe a secret account hidden here,
واكتشفت أنه ربما يوجد حساب سري مخفي هنا،
but I didn't find it yet.
ولكنني لم أجده بعد.
I suspect
انا اشتبه
there's a hidden space here.
هناك مساحة مخفية هنا.
I'll keep looking.
سأستمر في البحث.
I knew there was a secret chamber.
لقد عرفت أن هناك غرفة سرية.
Come on.
تعال.
Help me look for it.
ساعدني في البحث عنه.
Lord Yi took so many bribes.
لقد أخذ اللورد يي الكثير من الرشاوى.
Once we find the secret account,
بمجرد العثور على الحساب السري،
he can never deny it before His Majesty.
فهو لا يستطيع أن ينكر ذلك أمام جلالته أبدًا.
It's here.
إنه هنا.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
Quick. Get out of here first.
سريعًا، اخرج من هنا أولًا.
(No way, the lock.)
(لا سبيل للقفل.)
(What to do? He's going to see us.)
(ماذا نفعل؟ إنه سوف يرانا.)
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Let's get out of here.
دعونا نخرج من هنا.
He almost found us.
لقد كاد أن يجدنا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
That day
ذلك اليوم
when you pulled out a golden feather, I was conscious.
عندما سحبت ريشة ذهبية، كنت واعيًا.
The golden feather must be important
الريشة الذهبية يجب أن تكون مهمة
to Phoenix Divine Beasts, right?
إلى فينيكس الوحوش الإلهية، أليس كذلك؟
If he ever takes over your body again,
إذا استولى على جسدك مرة أخرى،
I can help you.
أستطيع مساعدتك.
You know?
أنت تعرف؟
I know there are two souls in your body,
أعلم أن هناك روحين في جسدك،
and my kiss
وقبلتي
can keep it at bay.
يمكن أن تبقيه تحت السيطرة.
There won't be another time like this.
لن يكون هناك وقت آخر مثل هذا.
I help you
انا اساعدك
only for the Xuanzhu Jade.
مخصص فقط لـ Xuanzhu Jade.
What's wrong with me?
ماذا بي؟
(After the twin cultivation on the full moon night,)
(بعد الزراعة التوأمية في ليلة اكتمال القمر)
(she will be sacrificed once the pact is complete.)
(سيتم التضحية بها بمجرد اكتمال العهد.)
(For the sake of the clan, I mustn't have feelings for her.)
(من أجل العشيرة، لا بد وأنني لا أشعر تجاهها بأي مشاعر.)
Ah, I've lost my mind.
اه لقد فقدت عقلي.
Could it be...
هل يمكن أن يكون...
"Twin cultivation on the full moon night.
"الزراعة التوأم في ليلة اكتمال القمر.
Whoever betrays
من خان
will suffer backlashes."
"سوف تعاني من ردود فعل عكسية."
Does that mean
هل هذا يعني
he and I...
هو وأنا...
You...
أنت...
- I...
- أنا...
It's late. Why are you in my room?
لقد تأخر الوقت. لماذا أنت في غرفتي؟
I couldn't sleep,
لم أستطع النوم
so I passed by.
لذلك مررت.
You...
أنت...
You're dressed so boldly,
أنت ترتدي ملابس جريئة للغاية،
wandering around at midnight.
التجوال في منتصف الليل.
The Scarlet Flame Clan
عشيرة اللهب القرمزي
has warm bodies.
لديه أجسام دافئة.
I should get going.
ينبغي لي أن أذهب.
Wait. Don't go.
انتظر.لا تذهب.
No. Just go.
لا، فقط اذهب.
Do you want me to come in
هل تريدني أن أدخل؟
or to go out?
أو الخروج؟
Backlash is nothing.
رد الفعل ليس شيئا.
I won't believe I can't get through it.
لن أصدق أنني لا أستطيع تجاوز ذلك.
Sleep.
ينام.
Just sleep and it'll be fine.
فقط نم وسيكون كل شيء على ما يرام.
(Calm down.)
(اهدأ.)
I...
أنا...
I didn't
لم أكن
mean it.
أعني ذلك.
I didn't mean to summon you.
لم أقصد أن أستدعيك.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
You started it.
لقد بدأتها.
=Twin Fates= =End of Episode 7=
=مصيران توأمان= =نهاية الحلقة 7=
♪In a world of sorrows, every encounter is fleeting♪
♪في عالم من الأحزان، كل لقاء عابر♪
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
♪الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي♪
♪In dreams, mountains and flowers are as beautiful as jade♪
♪في الأحلام، الجبال والزهور جميلة مثل اليشم♪
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
♪كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم♪
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
♪مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة♪
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
♪على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه؟♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
♪ترك خطين وحيدين فقط♪
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
♪زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب السنونو نظرتي الحسود♪
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
♪مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه♪
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪